Finding Aid for the Mary Anne Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Mary Anne Smith Papers
1964-1985
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0401
9.18 linear_feet
Biographical Sketch
Social activist Mary Anne Smith was born in 1945, the oldest of three children. In 1961 she attended an interracial, interdenominational church camp which laid the foundation for her future in activism. The formative experiences of that summer marked the beginning of Mary Anne’s interest in civil rights. From 1964-1967 Mary Anne attended Vanderbilt University where she studied classics and her interest in activism grew.
In the years following college, Mary Anne continued to read literature on race and the Vietnam War. Her goal was not political, however, but religious. She planned to teach Latin and then attend Divinity School. When Martin Luther King Jr. was assassinated, she felt that people she knew in the church reacted in a way with which she disagreed. At this point, she decided that her future would be in political activism.
1968-1972 were very intense years of study and social involvement for Mary Anne. She studied heavily the overarching power structure involved in racism, sexism, classism, and capitalism. During this period she became particularly interested in Marxism and socialist societies. Along with seven other women, Mary Anne became part of a group call the Women’s Anti-Imperial Collective. This small group would meet to exchange feminist and anti-imperialist ideas as well as try to raise consciousness surrounding these ideas in the larger community. During this time she was also involved with anti-war protests as well as the worker’s rights movement.
Mary Anne was particularly interested in changing the direction of the United States through Marxism. Her hope was to find a place in which socialism was working in order to find an example for this country. She became involved in the U.S. – China Friendship Association and was interested in bolstering the relationship between these two countries. As coordinator of the Nashville chapter of the group, Mary Anne spoke at gathering, planned fundraisers, and dispersed literature in the community. In 1976 she had the opportunity to travel to China with some of the group members in a leadership role. As leader, she was able to meet with all of the Chinese leaders with whom they came in contact. She had a particular interest in life for women in China, and based on her experience felt that women there had many of the same struggles and ideas as women in the U.S. The goal of the trip for the Association was to build relationships between their organization and organizations in China and, for Mary Anne, to learn ways the U.S. could look to China as an example.
After the trip Mary Anne returned to Nashville. She and her first husband separated, and she worked at various places in the city. In 1978, she decided to move to Atlanta and there continued her involvement in social activism.
Scope and Content Note
Comprised of 17 boxes (7.5 lin. feet) and includes subjects on China, nuclear war and weapons, women’s rights, worker’s rights, socialism, and diaries and correspondence.
The China records contain information about the U.S. – China People’s Friendship Association. This section also contains records from the group’s trip to China, led by Smith, in 1976. The documents in this section range in dates from 1975-1977.
Another series contains information about nuclear war and weapons and ranges in date from 1982 to 1987. These materials are largely magazine and newspaper articles which discuss the danger of nuclear war and weapons as well as peaceable alternatives.
The collection also contains three series’ containing Mary Anne’s materials regarding women’s rights, worker’s rights, and other liberation movements. The majority of the pieces included in these series are magazines, articles, personal notes, flyers and correspondence. These three series represent 1968 to 1972, the years in which Mary Ann learned about and was involved in a numbers of groups and movements.
The last series contains Mary Anne’s personal notebooks, letters, calendars, and various miscellaneous items. Of particular interest to the researcher may be her extensive collection of buttons, her Mao-style hats, and three audio cassettes which contain an interview with Mary Anne from 2001.
Provenance Statement
This collection was donated by Mary Anne Smith to Vanderbilt Special Collections in 2001.
- China
  - A Brief History of the United States by Shih Chan, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Banking and Financial Environment of the People’s Republic of China by Richard H. Pettway, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles on China; US – China Diplomatic Relations; Cultural Resources for Normalization Programs; US – China People Friendship Association. Southern Newsletter. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Convention Planning Materials US – China People’s Friendship Association, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - U.S. China Diplomatic Relations Reference Materials Normalization, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Issues and Position Papers; U.S. China People’s Friendship Association (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - U.S. -- China People’s Friendship Association Southern Region Newsletter, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - U.S.-- China People’s Friendship Association National Newsletter (5 issues), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - U.S. – China People’s Friendship Association of Nashville, materials (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - U.S. – China People’s Friendship Association 3rd Annual Convention, Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - U.S. – China People’s Friendship Association 4th Annual Convention, Atlanta, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - U.S. – China People’s Friendship Association Convention, Chicago; New China Magazine Proposal, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - U.S. – China Report, Chinese New Year Celebration flyer, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- China
  - Admit China to the Olympics Campaign, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Outreach to Working Class Minorities in China – U.S. People’s Friendship Association (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - U.S China People’s Friendship Association Southern Newsletter – 1978, National Newsletter, 1978, Guidelines for a New USPCFA Local, Notebook of Mary Anne Downey (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Information related to 1976 Southern Regional Activist Tour, (July 15th- August 7th, 1976) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Materials on earthquake, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - U.S – China People’s Friendship Association Southern Regional Conference at TSU, May 26-28 1978 (1) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - U.S – China People’s Friendship Association Southern Regional Conference at TSU, May 26-28 1978 (2) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - China’s Foreign Policy – An Outline compiled by C. Clark Kissinger, Chicago, August 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - China and U.S. – Publication of the U.S – China People’s Friendship Association, New York and other publications (Deep Roots in Two Countries), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- China
  - Political Report to the 11th National Congress of the Communist Party of China (Aug. 18th, 1977) and other materials on China (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Peking Review, Nov. 1975-Sept. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Peking Review, Sept. - Oct..1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Peking Review, Oct. 29 – Nov. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Peking Review, Dec. 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Peking Review, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - China – Hsinhua News Agency News Bulletin Sunday July 18, 1976; U.S.—China Report Nov./Dec. 1975; China Today; Other (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Diary/Notebook; Tour Information Brochures; U.S. – China People’s Friendship Assn. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - China – U.S. Notebook USCPFS Convention 1977; Hsinhua News Agency Bulletin 1976. U.S – China Report, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - China – Photocopy of letter (Peking Hotel, China) Mary Anne to her mother, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - China – Evaluation Forms for Activist Tour, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nuclear War and Weapons
  - Freeze Sum-up, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Freeze materials – Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign, 1983-85 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - “The Costs and Consequences of Reagan’s Military Build-up” A Report to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers AFL-CIO, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Notecards on Nuclear Weapons and War Talk given by Mary Anne Smith (undated) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Notes on nuclear weapons and war (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlets on nuclear war, weapons (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - South End Press – The Alternative (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Beyond War – information packet (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Freeze/Jobs with Peace Campaign, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Voice Literary Supplement No.15, March 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Mother Jones, May 1987; Aug./Sept. 1987; Oct. 1987; Nov. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Nation, April 14, 1984; April 21, 1984; May 5, 1984; May 12, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Political Solutions – a Publication of IDA/DSA Nashville, # 1, 4, 7, 9, 1986-87 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Articles from Psychology Today, 1981-82 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Magazine articles on Radiation; EST; Cultural Civil War; Living Health and Street Free; Teamster Madness; It’s Time for Management Concessions (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Utne Reader – The Best of the Alternative Press (1982); Have a Natural Christmas (1985) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Monitor – a Publication of the Center for Democratic Renewal, (December 1986, May 1987) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Articles on nuclear war/weapons, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Notebook of Materials on Nuclear War, training sessions, talks, resources, etc. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Women’s Rights
  - (from Nuclear War section) Citizen’s Network Speaker/Trainer Kit (Includes Briefing papers – Union of Concerned Scientists, Physicians for Social Responsibility and personal notes) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Magazines – Southern Exposure, May June 1984; Southern Feminist, Spring 1987 ;Hurricane Alize – A Feminist Review, no date; Newsweek, Geraldine Ferraro, Oct. 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Women’s City Country Chronicle, Issues 1, 6, 8, 9, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Psychology Today, 2 issues, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Women’s Free Express; Statistics on women, rape article, flyer from Women’s Cultural Festival, 1972-73 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Women’s Liberation Through Socialist Revolution; Socialist-Feminist Conference Materials (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - East West Journal – August/November, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Women’s Rights – pamphlets, newsletters – mid, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Gender Gap, June 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Notes on Socialist Feminist Theory (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Women in New China; Women Behind Bars; Feminist Cultural Network, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Socialist/Feminist Songbook; Industrial Workers of the World Songs; Articles “Women Together and Me Alone”, an others, San Francisco Women’s Center Newsletter and other Newsletters, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Worker’s Issues
  - Point of Production – Official Voice of the Black Worker’s Congress, May 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - The Communist, Chicago, Detroit, 8 Issues, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - The Communist – Worker’s Congress, Chicago, IL, 6 issues, 1975-76 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Worker’s Issues—Avco Nashville Bridge, Newsletter Pushin On (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Worker’s Issues – Notebook, Notes (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Worker’s Issues – Pamphlets: “On Educational Stages of Student Struggle” Rev. Worker’s Congress – “No Real Change Through Elections!” Midwest Academy – “Training in Direct Action Organizing” (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SCEF Materials (Southern Conference Educational Fund) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SCEF Materials (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - United League Materials (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Southern Patriot – published by SCEF, April 1975 – Sept 1976, Dec 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Southern Struggle – published by SCEF, Jan. 1977 – April 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Southern Struggle – published by SCEF, May-June 1978- Nov./Dec. 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Southern Struggle – published by SCEF, Jan-Feb 1979 – April 1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Southern Struggle – published by SCEF, Feb – Aug 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Draft work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Index to Notes, China Tour, July 15- August 7, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Worker’s Issues and Socialism
  - CCA Today (Container Corporation of America) Monthly Reports, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Restaurants, Cotton Garment and Allied Industries – Union Organizing and Benefits (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - “Dialectical and Historical Materialism” by Joseph Stalin (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - “Socialism: Utopian and Scientific” (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - “For a Revolutionary Position on the Negro Question” (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Weather Underground Organization – Osawatomic (1975); Prairie Fire (1974) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Washington Watch (1976); The People United (1876); Black and White Unite and Fight Prison News (1976) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Campaigner – published by the Nation Caucus of the Labor Committees, Sept/Oct 1973; Nov 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - A Selection from the Red Papers; War and Revolution; The Chicano Struggle and the Struggle for Socialism (1975); 200 Years is Long Enough, (June 1976) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Metro Soundings (April 1974); “Native American Resistance”; “The Basket Makers of Middle Tennessee”; “Economics” (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Red Papers 8 – “China Advances on the Socialist Road” Revolutionary Workers Headquarters (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 4 Issues of Workers Viewpoint, May 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Liberation (March 1972); The Red Papers; Red Earth; Workers Viewpoint, April-May 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Other Liberation Movements
  - Book Catalogs; Third World Cinema Catalog, 1975-76 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco Survival Manual 74-75; 1975 Peoples’ Party National Convention Call; On the Line, June 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Various Newsletters – Committee for Prisoner Support; The Leveller (April 1969); Jobs for Veterans’ Report (May 1975); Station Notes (April 1975) KPFA-FM94; Draft information (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Breakdown, 1970 (5 copies) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Collective works – Journal of Independent Marxist-Leninist Organizations, Aug. 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper On the Line—Worker Unity Organization St. Louis, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Information from CWLU (Chicago Women’s Liberation Union) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Motive Vol. XXIX, Nos. 6 & 7 (published by United Methodist Church), March/April 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Plexus, A Bay Area Women’s Newspaper, November/December 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Esalon Catalog, April-June 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Women’s Newsletters and Newspapers, 1974-75 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper -- The Black Panther, Sat. August 21, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers Untitled and Free Press Boston, March 23, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings Women’s Liberation Movement (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Women’s Liberation Movement (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings Women’s Liberation Movement (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Women’s Movement Letters; “Half of America” Female Liberation of Nashville – October 1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Women’s Liberation Movement various papers (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Notebook and SCEF (Southern Conference Educational Fund) Papers (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Articles Radical Politics (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Publications
  - Newspapers –The Nashville Rag; Kudzu, June/Sept./Oct. 1970; The Great Speckled Bird, July 24 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The Women’s Free Express; Urban Renewal; Public Hearing Welfare Rights (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Schools magazine – Spring, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets and Newsletters Women’s and Children’s Issues (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Committee of Justice in Mississippi Papers and Notebook (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbilt Hustler, April 23,30 1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Fight Back News (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Organizing materials (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Appalachian People’s History Book (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - People’s Appalachia Spring – 1971; Mountain Life and Work - March 1971; The Hillbillys: A Book for Children; The Adventures of Super Jay (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - The Pied Piper by William Glennon (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Motive volume 32, numbers 1 and 2, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Notes from the 3rd Year: Women’s Liberation, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - MS, June 1973, July 1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Publications
  - Newspapers Common Sense, Leviathan, Shelter, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers Southern Legal Action Movement; Newsletter of the Union for Radical Political Economics, October 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Liberation, Feb. 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter – Tennessee Valley Socialist, May-July 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers Women’s and Revolution (September/October 1971); Womankind (February 1973); Union Week (March-April 1975) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Women’s Liberation Revolution (3 articles) published by Socialist Workshop (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers Off Our Backs—A Women’s News Journal (April 76); Change—A Working Woman’s Newspaper (June-Oct 1971); The African World, (March 1975) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Political Economy of Women—The Review of Radical Political Economy, July 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ramparts, April, September, May 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Women’s Free Express, March 1974, August-September 1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Vocations for Social Change, November-December 1970; Human Behavior – November 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Today’s World in the Tennessean, Oct. 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - “A Talk on Sexual Politics” given by Gwen Patton, March 9, 1971 at the Control, Conflict, Change Seminar (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Women’s and Worker’s Movements
  - Anti-Imperialist Information; Toronto Conference Information (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Women’s Movement Newsletters and other publications (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters Indochina Peace Campaign Report; Phi Delta Kappa, April 1972; Open Letter to Jake’s Foundry Company (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Women’s Issues “On the Liberation of Women in Albania”; Nashville Women’s Center, July 12, 1973; others, including childcare materials (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Women’s movement CLUW contacts (Coalition of Labor Union Women) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - N.O.W.—Nashville Chapter—Feb. 1972; Nashville Women’s Center (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - California Women’s Movement Newsletter, (April 1975) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Women’s Liberation—Various Papers (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Free Palestine— March 1971; The Real Dirt June 1972; Cops are Hired to Enforce the Laws (People’s Press) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Legal First Air; Survival School System; People’s Food Co-op (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Tourist Boycott; People Inc., The Insurgent Sociologist (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - A Historical Discography of Black American Music (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - “The Wageless Slave and the Proletarian” (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - People’s Health —September 1975; Transmission—Voice of the Health Workers —September 1975; and other workers’ papers (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Worker’s Rights
  - Bakery, Confectionary, and Tobacco Workers’ International Union—Reports and News (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW)—news and notes (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - CLUW news and notes (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Notebook—CLUW, Education Committee, Labor (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - CLUW notebook (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CLUW, National Association of Working Women, Women for Economic Justice—Papers, news and reports (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CLUW notes, bulletins, reports (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - OSHA, Union, Labor, Economic pamphlets (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Worker’s Rights
  - CLUW News, reports, by-laws (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - CLUW News, bulletins, etc. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Daycare Dilemma: Parents, Employers, and Communities Search for Solutions, April 18, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Daycare Dilemma: Parents, Employers, and Communities Search for Solutions, April 18, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Info from Amalgamated Transit Union —Union Busting, Golden State Foods, etc. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Health of Women at Work —a bibliography (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Various pamphlets, booklets—Why Unions?, CLUW Constitution, Sexual Harassment, Legal Status of Women in Tennessee (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO: The Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions; National Labor Committee, El Salvador (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Worker’s Rights
  - Occupational Health and Safety Info (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta Peace Alliance—Anti-War info (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Citizens for a Healthy Environment (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Women’s Issues: Women and Employment in the South—ACLU (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Women’s Occupational Health Resource Center—information fact sheets, etc. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Non-sexist Children’s books: A Bibliography (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Buttons, pamphlets, newspaper clippings of rallies (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - “Country Women” magazines—issues 15,19,22,23,24 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Union organization workshop materials—notes, worksheets, announcements (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - CLUW correspondence—financial reports, meetings, other (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Worker’s Rights and Other
  - CLUW Correspondence—newsletters, announcements, etc. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - CLUW News (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - BC&T News, reports, correspondence (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - BC&T pamphlets, manuals, and meeting log (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ms. Magazine on WLM and FBI (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Southern Exposure, summer 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Anti-war movement materials (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Personal Records
  - Correspondence to George Downey family from Mary Anne and Gregg Downey, 1969-1971 (4) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Covey Card from Linda Stele (Chicago Theological Seminary); Mary Anne Smith in anti-nuke demo; Mary Anne Smith CLUE in Nashville (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Day Planners, 1964/65 and 1965/66 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Day Planners, 1972, 1973, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Calendars, 1975 and 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Day Planners, 1977 and 1978 (2) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Day Planners, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Day Planners, 1980 and 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Personal Records, 1 VHS tape—Star Wars 1 Audio-cassette tape – I. 5 year Defense Plan II. The Organizations III. Building Security IV. Sources of Hope 3 audio-cassette tapes – Ed Hamlett interviews Mary Anne Smith, Dec. 26, 2001 2 Chinese Mao-style hats 1 Oversize Mother Jones Calendar 1972 1 Oversize 1982 Calendar—Women’s Occupational Health Resource Center Buttons and Pins 227 59 cents A Woman’s Place is in Her Union – 2 Abortion A Woman’s Right to Choose: March on Washington DC and SF Nov. 20 Across America We Will be Heard Labor Day 1983 America Wins with Mondale—Communications Workers of America – 2 Atlanta Urban League 1991 NUL Conference Bread not Bombs Capitalism fouls things up—Vote Socialist Workers ERA Yes Failure is Impossible Food Prices High? Eat the Rich Free Angela Free Angela and All Political Prisoners Free Joann Little Free the Knoxville 22 Friendship First Competition Second FSLN por la Paz Huelga Don’t Buy Grapes UF WOC AFL-CIO Jesse Jackson ’88 – 2 Jobs with Peace Listen to Women for a Change Lorenzo Mao Head Mondale Ferraro – 2 NAACP march Against Racism in South Africa March 18th, 1870, Nashville, TN Nashville Boycotts Non-Union Grapes Nice Ending Proud to be BCT PAC SPH Stop I-440 Support the Black Liberation Movement—Wrightsville, GA Tierra O Muerte—Emiliano Zapata U.S.—China People’s Friendship Union Committee- Clothing and Textile Workers United Garment Workers of America Since 1891 United Steelworkers of America—Member Victory to the People of Southern Africa! Africa Liberation Day Coalition Warning Schools Spread Sexism Wastewatcher Women Power Pin World Peace Young for Atlanta
  - Day Planners, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Day Planners, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)